Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1912-(1915-1921); Series III; 7 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - Treaty of Versailles
    - Miscellaneous annotations: part VIII (mimeo), [1919] (Box 36, Folder 818)
    - Miscellaneous annotations: parts II, V, VI, XI, XIV, XV (mimeo), [1919] (Box 36, Folder 819)
    - Miscellaneous annotations: part X (mimeo), [1919] (Box 36, Folder 820)
    - Joseph Reinach: article, "Across the Ocean," LeFigaro, 1919 Dec 11 (copy, in translation), 1920 January 3 (Box 36, Folder 821)
    - Memoranda re: legal issues raised by alternatives to ratification, 1920 March 10, [1920] (Box 36, Folder 822)
    - "Comment on the Fourteen Reservations to the Peace Treaty,", undated (Box 36, Folder 823)
  - Turkey
    - William H. Buckler: memorandum re: "Partition of Asia Minor,", 1919 July 30 (Box 36, Folder 824)
    - William H. Buckler: memorandum re: "Evacuation of Asia Minor by Greeks and Italians,", 1919 September 23 (Box 36, Folder 825)
    - William H. Buckler: memorandum re: "Views of Haim Nahum, Grand Rabbi of Turkey" (with covering memorandum), 1919 October 6, 7 (Box 36, Folder 826)
    - Naval intelligence report re: "Proclamation by Sivas Nationalist Congress" (carbon), 1919 October 10 (Box 36, Folder 827)
    - William H. Buckler: memorandum re: "interview with Ahmed Riza, former President of the Turkish Senate" (with covering memorandum), 1919 November 13 (Box 36, Folder 828)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1919-1920 (Box 36, Folder 829)
    - Frank L. Polk: draft cables to Hugh C. Wallace re: treaty negotiations (with revision by Alvey A. Adee), 1920 [pre-March 6], March 6 (Box 36, Folder 830)
    - Alvey A. Adee: memorandum re: terms of treaty proposed by Jusserand, [1920 March 13-29] (Box 36, Folder 831)
    - Note to Jusserand re: proposed terms of treaty (preliminary draft, final draft, press release), 1920 March 13-30 (Box 36, Folder 832)
    - "Memorandum for Mr. Polk Regarding Proposed Treaty with Turkey,", 1920 March 15 (Box 36, Folder 833)
    - Supreme Council: "Answer to American Note" re: treaty negotiations (copy), 1920 April 26 (Box 36, Folder 834)
    - Memorandum re: the Supreme Council's reply about treaty negotiations, 1920 May 10 (Box 36, Folder 835)
  - Ukraine
    - Ukrainian Delegation: memorandum re: the economic, political, and military situation in the Ukraine, 1919 August 7, 13 (Box 36, Folder 836)
    - Memoranda and letters re: supplies to the Ukraine, 1919 August 27 - December 3 (Box 36, Folder 837)
    - American Red Cross: letters re: conditions in the Ukraine (copies, with covering letter), 1919 October 6-22 (Box 36, Folder 838)
  - United States Food Administration
    - Miscellaneous letters and cables, 1917-1921 (Box 36, Folder 839)
  - Uruguay
    - Frank L. Polk: diary memoranda re: conversations with the Uruguayan minister, 1916 July 13-20 (Box 36, Folder 840)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, 1917-1918 (Box 36, Folder 841)
  - Venezuela
    - Memoranda re: Theodore Roosevelt's role in arranging arbitration of British, French, and Italian claims against Venezuela in 1902, 1916 October 2 (Box 36, Folder 842)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1917-1919 (Box 36, Folder 843)
    - Ferdinand L. Mayer: memorandum re: "The present conditions in Venezuela,", 1918 April 27 (Box 36, Folder 844)
    - Leo S. Rowe: memoranda exchanged with Polk re: rank of the German ambassador in Caracas, 1920 January 2, February 3 (Box 36, Folder 845)
  - War Administration and Military Developments
    - Correspondence re: shipment of arms and ammunition on the transport Dix (copies, with. covering letters), 1915 December 3-16 (Box 37, Folder 846)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1917-1918, undated (Box 37, Folder 847)
    - Tasker H. Bliss: cables to the Adjutant General (copies), 1918 February 20 - August 24 (Box 37, Folder 848)
    - Cables from the French forces re: the situation in the vicinity of the Somme and Montidier (copies, some in French), 1918 March 26 - April 5 (Box 37, Folder 849)
    - Cables from the American forces re: the situation in France (copies), 1918 October 9-16 (Box 37, Folder 850)
    - Arthur J. Balfour: "Memorandum for the War Cabinet: Armies and Economics, Being Reflexions on Some Aspects of the Allied Situation on July 27, 1919" (copy, sent to Polk with covering letter by George R. Clerk), 1919 July 27, August 4 (Box 37, Folder 851)
    - War Department, Purchase, Storage and Traffic Division: letter to G. Howland Shaw re: sale of surplus to European governments, 1919 September 3 (Box 37, Folder 852)
    - Frank L. Polk: memorandum to Christian Herter re: French demand for U.S. representation on the [Allied Military Council?], 1920 January 15 (Box 37, Folder 853)
  - War Trade Board
    - Trade Letter Bulletin, nos. 75, 79, 80, 1918 October 11, 26, 30 (Box 37, Folder 854)
    - Memoranda re: handling cables, 1918 November 15 - December 12 (Box 37, Folder 855)
  - Western Europe
    - State Department, Division of Western European Affairs: "Daily Report,", 1919 March 3, 4 (Box 37, Folder 856)
  - Yugoslavia
    - Memorandum, "Serbian Credits" (carbon), 1918 July 24 (Box 37, Folder 857)
    - Cables to the American representative in Corfu, 1918 (Box 37, Folder 858)
    - Serb-Croat-Slovene mass meeting, New York City: letters and resolution, 1919 February 20, 26 (Box 37, Folder 859)
    - [John Foster Dulles?]: memorandum and covering letter re: retention in the Adriatic of Austro-Hungarian tonnage (carbons of originals sent to Balfour by Polk), 1919 August 6 (Box 37, Folder 860)
    - Douglas W. Johnson: memorandum to the U.S. Commissioners Plenipotentiary re: "Proposed plebiscite in Marburg region,", 1919 August 26 (Box 37, Folder 861)
    - Memorandum of the Serbo-Croat-Slovene Peace Delegation Regarding the Release of Yugoslav Shipping (with covering letter by Ante Trumbić), 1919 September 1 (Box 37, Folder 862)
    - Allen W. Dulles: memorandum re: the Yugoslavian memorandum of Sep 1, 1919 September 4 (Box 37, Folder 863)
    - "Notes of a Conversation between Dr. Trumbich, of the Yugo-Slav Delegation, and Mr. Frazier, on September 17th, 1919,", 1919 September 17 (Box 37, Folder 864)
    - Robert Lansing: cable to Polk re: disposition of Austro-Hungarian tonnage, 1919 October 5 (Box 37, Folder 865)
    - Allen W. Dulles: memorandum re: positions of Berthelot and Vesnitch on the treatment of Macedonia, [1919 November 3?] (Box 37, Folder 866)
    - Ivan Shvegel: letter to G. Howland Shaw re: meeting with Polk, 1919 December 6 (Box 37, Folder 867)
    - Elizabeth S. (Potter) Polk: memorandum re: Polk's authorship of a speech about Yugoslavia delivered by Wilson, 1920 Feb, undated (Box 37, Folder 868)
  - Non-circulating-duplicates of meeting notes of heads of the Five Great Powers (H.D. 23-65), 1919 August 4-October 2 (Box 66)
  - Non-circulating duplicates of meeting notes of the heads of the Five Great Powers (H.D. 66-106), 1919 October 7-December 11 (Box 67)
- Chronological Files, 1915-1919; Series IV; 2.5 linear feet (7 boxes)
  Chronological Files has six sections: Telephone Logs, Cables to Ammission, Cables from Ammission, Interviews with the French Press, Supreme Council Resolutions, and Ammission Reports and Bulletins. Each is in chronological order.
  - Telephone Logs
    - 1915 October 5 - 1916 August 31, 1916 November 1-14 (Box 38, Folder 1-29)
    - 1916 November 15 - 1917 January 14 (Box 39, Folder 30-42)
    - 1917 May 7-16 (correspondence re: legality of wiretaps) (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Cables to Ammission
    - 1918 October 23 - 1919 December 8 (Box 40, Folder 44-73)
  - Cables from Ammission
    - 1918 October 28 - 1919 September 11 (Box 41, Folder 74-100)
    - 1919 September 12 - December 20 (Box 42, Folder 101-126)
  - Interviews with the French Press
    - 1919 August 1 - December 9 (Box 42, Folder 127-130)
  - Supreme Council Resolutions
    - No. O-V, 1919 July 5-12 (Box 43, Folder 131)
    - No. 1-5, 1919 July 15-21 (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - No. 6-11, 1919 July 25-29 (Box 43, Folder 133)
    - No. 12-18, 1919 July 30 - August 6 (Box 43, Folder 134)
    - No. 26-30, 1919 August 7-13 (Box 43, Folder 135)
    - No. 31-35, 1919 August 14-21 (Box 43, Folder 136)
    - No. 36-40, 1919 August 22-27 (Box 43, Folder 137)
    - No. 41-46, 1919 August 28 - September 3 (Box 43, Folder 138)
    - No. 47-53, 1919 September 4-15 (Box 43, Folder 139)
    - No. 55-60, 1919 September 17-25 (Box 43, Folder 140)
    - No. 61-66, 1919 September 26 - October 7 (Box 43, Folder 141)
    - No. 67-70, 1919 October 10-15 (Box 43, Folder 142)
    - No. 71-75, 77, 1919 October 16-28 (Box 43, Folder 143)
  - Ammission Reports and Bulletins
    - Reports, no. 7-10, 1919 April 28 - May 22 (Box 44, Folder 144)
    - Reports, no. 12-26, 1919 May 23-28 (Box 44, Folder 145)
    - Reports, no. 27-33, 1919 May 28-31 (Box 44, Folder 146)
    - Reports, no. 34-41, 1919 June 1-12 (Box 44, Folder 147)
    - Reports, no. 42-46, 1919 June 12-16 (Box 44, Folder 148)
    - Reports, no. 47-54, 1919 June 16-29 (Box 44, Folder 149)
    - Reports, no. 76, 107, 108, 113, 1919 June 5, 16, 17 (Box 44, Folder 150)
    - Bulletins, no. 904-905, 1919 September 16 (Box 44, Folder 151)
    - Bulletin, no. 908, 1919 September 17 (Box 44, Folder 152)
    - Bulletin, no. 910, 1919 September 18 (Box 44, Folder 153)
    - Bulletins, no. 993-997, 1919 October 2 (Box 44, Folder 154)
    - Bulletin, no. 1000, 1919 October 6 (Box 44, Folder 155)
- Politics and Memorabilia, 1883-(1898-1941); Series V; 6 linear feet (19 boxes, 1 folio)
  Politics and Memorabilia has four sections: General; Programs, Invitations, Menus; Scrapbooks; and Card Index. The first three sections are in chronological order except that oversize items belonging to the General section are in a separate folio.
  The Card Index was prepared before the collection was reprocessed. Its locations (drawer numbers) correspond to those of the old register, and are no longer meaningful. But it also affords a detailed subject index to the correspondence, and may serve to supplement the partial index that follows in this register.
  - General
    - Report cards and miscellaneous printed matter, 1883-1900 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Spanish American War
      - Official papers, 1898 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Letters from friends, 1898, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, personal papers, 1898, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Quartermaster's records, 1898-1901, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - New York City, Board of Education: clippings and letters about the appointment, 1906-1910 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Municipal Civil Service Commission of the City of New York
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment, 1907 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Twenty-Fourth Annual Report, 1907 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letters and papers, 1907-1910 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, 1908-1909, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Speeches, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Marriage to Elizabeth Sturgis Potter: clippings, 1908 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Criminal Courts of the Charity Organization Society of the City of New York: article reprinted from Survey, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Index to file of political clippings, [1910s?] (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Democratic party: certificates of election to party office, 1910, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Collectorship of the Port of New York
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment (A-L), 1913 April - May (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment (M-Z), 1913 April - May (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Clippings, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Campaign speech, [1913?] (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - John Purroy Mitchel
      - Speech accepting the support of a fusion committee for mayor, [1913] (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - List of members of the "Fusion Committee" (annotated), [1913] (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Memorabilia, memorial speech, 1913-1928, undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Letters, clippings, and proceedings before the Lunacy Commission re: the attempted assassination, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Corporation Counsel of the City of New York
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Schedule of salaries in the Law Department, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Address to the Postmaster's Association of New York, [1914-1915?] (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Letter and statement re: purchase of Amsterdam Electric Light, Heat and Power Company stock by the Edison Electric Illuminating Company of Brooklyn, 1915 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - "Frank Lyon Polk" (editorial and photograph), Bench and Bar, new ser., X., no. 3, 1915 July (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - State Department
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment (A-H), 1915 August - October (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment (I-N), 1915 September - November (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - Letters of congratulation on the appointment (O-Z), 1915 September - October (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Certificates of appointment, identification cards, miscellaneous papers, 1915-1920, undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - Clippings, 1915-1920 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Democratic party of New York: printed list of delegates, [1916 post-April 4] (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Peace Conference
      - Miscellaneous papers re: trip to Verdun and Pointe-de-Grave, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 35)
      - Photographs of Polk, 1919, undated (Box 46, Folder 36)
        See also: box 48A
      - The Continental Daily Mail: The Peace Conference in Pictures, [1919] (Box 46, Folder 37)
      - Parody of minutes, [1919?] (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - State Department: letters about Polk's resignation, 1920 February - June (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - The Morning Star (humorous publication of the Evening Star Club), 1920 March 31 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Lester H. Woolsey: "Memorandum: Submarine Cables (Conference on Communications, Washington, October, 1920),", [1920 Oct?] (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Awards, 1920-1938 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Frank L. Polk for the National Association for the Protection of American Rights in Mexico: brief re: Campania Minera de Naica, S. A. vs. Stoppelli (mimeo), 1921 January 15, 25 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Allen W. Dulles: letter [to the Secretary of State?] re: Peace Treaty negotiations (copy), 1922 July 22 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Clippings, 1922-1923, undated (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - World War I: correspondence with scholars, 1922-1942 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Woodrow Wilson Foundation: miscellaneous papers, 1922, 1929-1939 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Edward M. House
      - et al.: The League of Nations Interpreted as a Present Reality, 1923 (Box 46, Folder 48)
      - The Freedom of the Seas, undated (Box 46)
    - Editorial, "To Fill an Obvious Need," Groton School Quarterly, Vol. 1, no. 1, 1923 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Presidential campaign, 1924
      - Letters, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 50)
      - Speeches, printed matter, miscellaneous papers, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 51)
      - Tally sheets, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 52)
      - Clippings, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine: typed report and printed program, 1925, undated (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Committee on Conservation: letters and reports, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - Eine neue Rede des Senators Robert L. Owen uberdie Kriegsschuldfrage. Gehalten vor der Foreign Policy Association in Boston am 27. Marz 1926 (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - Northern Pacific Railway: clippings and itinerary, 1927-1928 (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - Passport, German visa, 1929, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Davis Polk Wardwell Gardiner and Reed: rosters, newsletter, 1930-1939 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Roosevelt Business and Professional League, Lawyers' Division: correspondence re: membership on the Executive Committee, 1932 October 8-27 (Box 47, Folder 60)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations, Fifth Biennial Conference: miscellaneous papers, 1933 (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Frank L. Polk: letter to William Phillips re: border incident at El Paso, 1919, 1932 February 6, 8 (Box 47, Folder 62)
    - Davis Polk Wardwell Gardiner & Reed: Some of the Antecedents, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 63)
    - "Rockefeller Center and Money Depreciation" by Francis T. Christy, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 64)
    - Draft opinion re: Roosevelt's plan to pack the Supreme Court (carbon, edited), [1937] (Box 47, Folder 65)
    - Recollections of the Peace Conference by Comte de Saint Quentin, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 66)
    - Phillips Talbot's letters from India to W. S. Rogers, nos. 30-69 (copies), 1939-1941 (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - Remarks about British domination of U.S. foreign policy by J.Thorkelson, Congressional Record, annotated by Polk, 1939 October 11 (Box 47, Folder 68)
    - Memorial Day address by Ralph Gabriel, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 69)
    - Publications re: General Leonidas Polk, 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 70)
    - Speeches re: King Peter II of Yugoslavia, 1941, undated (Box 48, Folder 71)
    - "Memorandum on Reinsurance,", [1941?] (Box 48, Folder 72)
    - Clippings about Polk's death, 1943 (Box 48, Folder 73)
    - Printed memorial tribute by William Adams Delano, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 74)
    - Notebook re: international law, undated (Box 48, Folder 75)
    - Speeches, toasts, and lectures on political and foreign policy subjects, undated (Box 48, Folder 76)
    - Memorabilia, miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 48, Folder 77)
    - Certificates, 1911-1939 (Folder 48A)
    - Photographs
      - Polk reviewing troops, [1919] (Folder 48A)
      - Paderewski testimonial dinner, 1921 (Folder 48A)
      - Pilgrims Society dinner, 1924 (Folder 48A)
  - Programs, Invitations, Menus
    - 1901-1909, 1913 - 1917 June (Folder 48A, Folder 78-86)
    - 1917 September - 1925, 1929 - 1930 Nov, 1933-1935, 1937-1942, undated (Box 49, Folder 87-94)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1909-1914 (Box 50)
    - 1914 February 9-1915 January 21 (Box 51)
    - 1915 January-December (Box 52)
    - 1915 December-1916 October (Box 51)
    - 1916 November-1919 September (Box 53)
    - 1919 August-1920 March (Box 54)
  - Card Index
    - Explanatory notes and index (Box 55)
    - Career (employers, clubs, highlights, etc), honors, memorabilia (Box 55)
    - Correspondence: from Polk
      - A - M (Box 55)
      - Mc - Z (Box 56)
    - Correspondence: to Polk
      - A - H (Box 56)
      - T - Z (Box 57)
    - Peace Conference
      - A - E (Box 57)
      - F - S (Box 58)
      - T - Z (Box 59)
    - State Department
      - A - C (Box 59)
      - D - R (Box 60–61)
      - S - Z (Box 62)
    - Cross-reference file for subjects of correspondence
      - A - B (Box 62)
      - C - Z (Box 63)
    - Cross-reference file for letters enclosed with other letters
- Partial Index to Series I
  This is a list of correspondents whose letters were removed from Charles Seymour's subject arrangement of the Polk Papers (the residue of which is now the basis of Series III, Subject Files) and arranged alphabetically in what is now Series I, Correspondence. The names are arranged alphabetically by subject (as chosen by Seymour, and slightly different from the subjects used in Series III). The subjects also are in alphabetical order.
  Seymour did not arrange all correspondence by subject, and so this is only a partial subject index to Series I. Polk's most frequent correspondents are especially underrepresented.
  - Agriculture
    - Harrison, Floyd R., 1918
    - Houston, David F., 1918
  - Alien Property Custodian
    - Chandler, Percy M., 1918
    - Cravath and Henderson, 1918
    - Fordyce, Samuel W., Jr., 1919
    - Garvan, Francis P., 1919
    - Guaranty Trust Company, 1922
    - Palmer, A. Mitchell, 1918-1919
    - Palmer, Bradley W., 1919
  - Aliens
    - Crowder, Enoch H., 1917
    - Hayden, Carl V., 1917
    - McDuffie, Duncan, 1918
  - American Metal Company
    - Cobb, Zach Lamar, 1916
    - Crawford, Richard, 1916
  - Argentina
    - Baldwin, Joseph C., Jr., 1919
    - Lamont, Thomas W., 1917
    - Quintana, Federico, 1915
  - Armenia
    - Barton, James L., 1917
    - Beers, Lucius H., 1920
    - Bristol, Mark L., 1920-21
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1916-17
    - Moore, John Bassett, 1916
  - Armistice
    - Barclay, Colville, 1918
    - Patchin, Philip H., 1928
    - Saxe, John Godfrey, 1918
  - Army
    - Bosler, William D., 1917
    - Brady, Peter J., 1916
    - Brancker, W. G., 1918
    - Brown, Lucius P., 1918-1919
    - Brown, Samuel A., 1918
    - Cottenent, Rawlin L., 1917
    - Dooling, John T., 1919
    - Dowling, Frank L., 1919
    - Eldridge, Dudley G., 1919
    - Filley, O. B., 1918
    - Foster, Philip L., 1917
    - Gardner, Augustus P., 1917
    - Gore, Thomas P., 1919
    - Lee, Walter E., 1917
    - Potter, Robert S., 1917
    - Viviani, René R., 1919
  - Associated Press
    - Noyes, Frank B., 1917
    - Stone, Melville E., 1918
  - Attorney General
    - Gregory, Thomas W., 1915-1917
    - Warren, Charles, 1915, 1917
  - Australia
    - Fyfe, Hamilton, 1917
  - Balkans
    - Bourchier, James D., 1919
    - Bryce, James, 1919
    - Buxton, Noel, 1919
  - Baltic
    - Clemenceau, Georges, 1919
    - Seskis, Janis, 1919
  - Belgium
    - Armour, Norman, 1919
    - Bassompièrre, Alfred de, 1919
    - Cartier de Marchienne, Emile de, 1918-1919
    - Flood, Henry D., 1917
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1919
    - Legge, Alexander, 1919
    - Redfield, William C., 1918-1919
    - Sabin, Charles H., 1919
    - Stokes, Anson P., 1916-1917
    - Whitlock, Brand, 1915-1917
  - Brazil
    - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1918
    - Franklin, George S., 1919
    - Gama, Domicio da, 1916-1920
    - Helm, Edith B., 1920
    - Logan, Thomas F., 1918
    - Mallet-Prevost, Severo, 1919
  - Bulgaria
    - Dulles, Allen W., 1919
    - Panateroff, Stephan, 1916-1917, 1919
  - Canada
    - Ernst, Oswald H., 1918
    - Hamill, Charles H., 1919
    - Levy, Aaron J., 1917
  - Central Powers
    - Albert, Heindrich F., 1916-1917
    - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1917
    - Baker, Newton D., 1917
    - Battle, George Gordon, 1917
    - Bennet, William S., 1916
    - Bernstorff, Johann-Heinrich von, 1916-1917
    - Bielaski, A. Bruce, 1916
    - Blair, Woodbury, 1917
    - Bull, Henry W., 1916
    - Bullitt, William C., 1916
    - Business Training Corporation, 1916
    - Chandler, Percy M., 1917
    - Cravath, Paul D., 1917
    - Crocker, William T., 1917
    - Eastley, Ralph M., 1916, 1918
    - Eno, Henry L., 1917
    - Flood, Henry D., 1918
    - Gerard, James W., 1917
    - Graham, George S., 1917
    - Gregory, Thomas W., 1917
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1917
    - Haigh, Henry B., 1918
    - Herbster, Victor D., 1916
    - Heynen, Carl, 1917
    - Hooper, H. E., 1915-1916
    - Kent, W. C., 1918
    - Konta, Alexander, 1917
    - Lane, Franklin K., 1917
    - Marcosson, Isaac F., 1919
    - Marshall, H. Snowden, 1917
    - Morgan, Henry H., 1916-1917
    - Nieman, Lucius W., 1917
    - O'Brian, John L., 1918
    - Pou, Edward W., 1917
    - Sabin, Charles H., 1919
    - Schurz, Carl L., 1917
    - Tarnowski, ____, 1917
    - Toomer, W. M., 1917
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1920
    - Warren, Charles, 1915, 1917
    - Whitelock, Deming and Kemp, 1917
  - Chile
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1918
  - Codes
    - Speyer and Co., 1916
  - Columbia
    - Davis, Norman H., 1920-1921
    - Philip, Hoffman, 1919-1920
    - Rowe, Leo S., 1920
    - Urueta, Carlos A., 1920-1921
  - Commerce Department
    - Business Training Corporation, 1916
    - Nielsen, Fred K., 1916
    - Pratt, Edward E., 1916
    - Redfield, William C., 1916-1919
    - Van Norman, Louis E., 1919
  - Committee on Public Information
    - Björkman, Edwin, 1919
    - Blair, William McC., 1917
    - Creel, George, 1917-1918
  - Communications
    - Hood, Edwin M., 1920
    - Pyne, Percy R., 1919
    - Root, Elihu, Jr., 1920